Music
Yeah
Three thumbs down for my AVP
Three point five just to hear me sleep
I do like Joelle and me
She'll never ever get a ring for me
She on my line like we got a thunk on her
I don't know that it can't be deep
Ten hall bounds a tap of the shelf on her
Damn, I'm key
I don't think that she want me for me
Damn, am I tweaking?
All my little hide and yell
Quiet it down, I ain't lie to you
You get proud of it, times of it's profit if all
Tide and yell, I ain't flying with your love
Die for us, think to the quiet all
No, I ain't going for it, no
I don't know no, I just got all my days on my lungs some
I ain't going to bed to this globe
It's all all in my chest, it is closed
Get cold as December when I'm closed
It's a feet 12 inch, I don't go slow
Damn, just hold on
I better go out of here for me
Damn, I better run with her and I don't care
Damn, are you telling my side off?
God damn, you know I got, you know I got all my days on me
Three thumbs down for my every feet
Three point five just to help me sleep
I do like Joelle and me
She'll never ever get a ring for me
She on my line like we got a thunk on her
I don't know that it can't be deep
Ten hall bounds a tap of the shelf on her
Cause but it can't be cheap
Damn, I don't keep, I don't think that she want me for me
Damn, am I sweet?
Or am I low high to y'all?
Quiet it down, I ain't lying to y'all
You get proud of it, times of it's profit if all
High to y'all lying, flying with y'all
Down for a stick to the quiet all
I don't got much left, I'm talking all about myself
I know what's right was wrong, I got sound got much less
Let's get a little more hot
Run me out ill put the windows down
Run around telling that I'm my guy
Way in the head that you get different
What's it get this fun?
Like can I get this time?
I have six grams in there
I think I could get this hot
I don't think I'm gonna risk this one
The yolks ain't worth 50 bucks
You really miss me huh?
Didn't it feel real for once?
Take some time for my heavy feet
Take point five just to help me sleep
I do like Joelle and me
She'll never ever get a ring for me
She on my line like we got a thunk on her
If I'm not the cause but it can't be cheap
I don't say this you want me for me